I'm Yu Mura, 18 years old from Tokyo, Japan. I'm Shizuku Yamashita, 18 years old from Kyoto, Japan.
Sakurazaka46 third term students. 11 of us have walked together.
We were able to overcome the obstacles because we are 11.
This is the story of the two of us and the 11 of us.
Another story
Welcome to the final performance of the Ogurazaka 46 National Tour at Tokyo Dome!
Of course, on this day, all the 3rd term students were staring at the same stage.
I had great expectations and anxiety, wondering if I would be able to join such a wonderful group.
To be honest, I am full of anxiety and I don't know if I can do it.
But after seeing them on stage today, my desire to be like them became even stronger.
I will do my best until the presentation so that I can strengthen my weak self from now on.
Thank you very much for your time.
Sorry for keeping you waiting. Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
Sakurazaka, isn't it already Sakurazaka?
That's Yuuka indeed.
I'm really glad that you came to Sakurazaka.
Everyone is so cute. I'm so happy. Thank you.
I know that a lot of things are waiting for you from now on.
I know you have a lot of things ahead of you, but I want you to do your best in the things you decide to do.
I know you have a lot of things ahead of you, but I want you to do your best in what you decide to do.
I may think that I'm slow or that I'm not as fast as everyone else, but I keep trying.
I keep trying my best. I know there are people out there who are watching me.
I really value and cherish the people who support me.
I hope that you will keep working hard toward your dreams.
I'll be watching over you now that I'm Buddies.
I will always support you. Keep up the good work, it's beautiful.
Thank you for coming today. Thank you for coming today.
Thank you very much.
Yes, OK!
You're so cute!
Thank you!
You've got me looking forward to Sakuraza. Love it!
Everyone, listen to Captain Matsuda!
Good luck!
Thank you!
Murai-san and Yamashita-san are the same half of the group at the camp. They are two of the best dancers among the 11 of us.
Both of them can dance well, so please practice with confidence!
I think Yamashita-chan is the best dancer.
Dance
I have been dancing for 6 years.
but I haven't mastered the basics yet.
I don't have it.
If I say something like that, people will expect more from me.
I really think you two are the ultimate weapon.
No, I'm not good at it.
I'm not good at it.
Really.
No, no, no.
No, I'm not good.
Yes, I am.
I've been doing ballet for six years.
Two years of dance at a studio.
I was on the dance team for two years in high school.
I want to push myself as hard as I can.
I want to push myself as hard as I can and try to be as close to the seniors as possible.
What a contrast between the two of you!
What shall we do?
I'm going to take a normal picture first.
What should we do?
Let's see...
It's not leaking at all.
It's not leaking.
I don't know what to do.
Should we put it on the floor and take a picture?
Wait, but it only shows our feet.
No, no, no.
Fuji Park.
Thank you for watching.
You still don't move like a dancer.
I don't know how to say it, but it doesn't feel like a performer?
I'd like you to think about the distinction between an idol and a dancer.
Yes, let's work on that.
When you said I looked like a dancer, not an idol, that's what I remember most.
I was frankly frustrated, and the line between dancing like an idol and dancing like a dancer was very difficult, and I had a lot of trouble with it.
I want to be able to give a performance that will be recognized as an idol as I continue to work on it.
On the fourth day of the camp, when Mr. Takahiro came to see us.
Yamashita-san's body was at its limits.
Shall I put on my yoga mat for a while?
Should I rest now?
A little bit, yeah.
Are you okay?
No, I don't think so.
I'm just kind of embarrassed.
You don't do that?
No, I don't.
I know how you feel, but don't push yourself too hard.
There were some problems that only the two of us could share.
I knew that the time of the presentation would be different from everyone else's.
I often had to criticize.
That's what made me so sad.
I wasn't alone yet.
Yu-chan was there, so it was all right.
But for us, we announce a little later than everyone else.
I felt that, you know, and it's sad.
It's sad, isn't it?
When you realize that, let me out.
Oh, hey, you both have dance experience!Oh, hey, they both have dance experience!
I don't know. I'm under a lot of pressure.
I understand.
It's like, you know, I have to do it right.
That's a lot of pressure.
The first training day, I couldn't go because of my club activities.
I watched the video you sent me and practiced watching yours.
Really?
The van dance.
Really.
I'm so happy.
That's how I learned it.
Really?
Yeah, I did.
That's amazing. That's probably the best thing I've seen all day.
Really?
Yeah, I'm sure.
All 11 of us are going in the same direction.
We're just a little bit different.
[applause]
I want to sparkle.
All of us.
All together.
CAMERAS, CAMERAS
I found some yello or something on someone's doorstep.
A catcher with ants all around him.
I'll tell you what I got.
yuma
Yes, it's better.
It's better now.
Netta tummy
Ugly.
But
It's
vivid
treated
New
East and West
Hey
Cute
Who
is
Пот
I'm in a ca
dizzy
alie
too
Day
Go!
Cream
f
I'm sorry I said that.
I'm with you
Nah.
Mistake
At the end, two very strong guys. I can see them. They are the two members of Sakurazaka. These two seem to be very similar.
They look very much alike.
But their types are complete opposites.
Murai has great skills.
and by developing his skills, he can improve himself more and more.
Yamashita is the type of person who can dig deep into himself
Yamashita is the type of person who can dig deep into himself by immersing himself in a song more and more.
Yamashita, you have a lot of energy when you perform.
Yamashita has a lot of energy when he performs on stage, but his voice is a little quiet in everyday life.
When it comes to the future and the way Yamashita performs
I think it's going to become an attraction.
And when he's playing a game, he'll close his eyes
I close my eyes a little bit when I'm playing a game.
You may not be aware of it, but
You may not be aware of it, but normally you can keep your eyes open.
I close my eyes when my emotions move me.
It was good to see the link between your performance and your feelings.
And even though you said no to the last chorus
I could see the moment when you got into the last chorus.
I could see it with my eyes and it gave me a thrill.
So I think I have a zone.
When you perform, you need two kinds of physical strength.
Two physical strengths are needed to perform.
Physical fitness and mental fitness.
I want you to be aware of both of them and nurture them.
Murai, you were the loudest.
That's a very good thing.
I guess they said you're not good at putting emotion into it.
Maybe it's because I've always been a technical person.
But that doesn't mean you'll be able to put emotion into it right away.
I don't think you'll be able to do it all at once in three days.
You have more technique than anyone else in this room.
I have more technique than anyone else in this group, and I can pull more than anyone else.
First of all, you have to aim to become a person who can pull more than anyone else with technique.
I think it's good to learn how to put emotion into it.
I think it's a good idea to learn more and more about how to put emotion into it.
Maybe it's just a coincidence.
It's a bit of a coincidence, but there was a friction case in there.
It was in there.
Yeah, I don't have any clothes, I was doing this.
I think I have a lot of ideas on how to use my body in relation to the music.
Only because I'm a dancer.
I wanted you to aim for that more than anybody else.
After the camp, now we're going to make up a van with all 11 of us.
Maybe we could decide on one person to be like a dance leader and have that person take the lead.Maybe we could decide on one person to be the dance leader and have that person take the lead.
The issue that became clear was the lack of a dance leader.
I can notice things that are not in place, but I am not good at communicating in words, so I was not confident that I was suited for the position of dance leader.
So I could not run for the position of dance leader.
However, she was not the only dance leader.
Ogawa!
So Yuka took the time to par.
Nagi asked me if I wanted to be a dance leader with her. She told me that she wanted to be a dance leader with me.
I can notice things, but I'm not good at expressing them in words, so I wasn't sure if I could do it or not.
But I had a great desire to help everyone and to improve the quality of the performance, so I thought I would try to be a dance leader with Nagi.
I decided to try to be a dance leader with Nagi, and I made up my mind.
Yoo-chan is a very good dancer, so when we all had to dance together, it was easier for us to coordinate our dance moves.
In this way, the third-year students steadily perfected their dance.
This is 18-year-old Yu Murai, a senior in high school.
I am 18 years old and a senior in high school.
I was attracted to the seniors who had so many attractive qualities.
I applied for this audition because I was attracted by the seniors who have so many attractive qualities.
I would like to work hard together with my favorite seniors to create something even better.
I would like to work hard together with my favorite seniors so that we can create something even better.
I love them very much.
My name is Shunju Yamashita, a 17-year-old high school senior and a very popular girl.
I am very happy to be a member of my favorite group.
My hobby is to collect your fresh pictures.
Please keep in touch with me as more seniors are born.
Thank you very much.
These are the 11 members of the 3rd term. We will do our best from now on.
Se-no, I did my best! Whee!
And now
The 11 of us will unite our hearts and deliver the best performance we can now.
Please do so.
Hey!
Ladies and gentlemen, this is the store?
There's no way I can stay then.
Look at all the things
I thought you might like to see this.
We'll play hide-and-seek.
What's wrong with that?
What's good about it?
We all yawned and got hurt.
Hey!
What an important love story
I don't know when it started, I don't know what it means
Still, it's the best love of all
Someday it became my heart
where did they all go?
why do you want that kind of love?
Wait a minute.
You haven't met her.
I can see everything.
I mean, I'm the only one with feelings for her.
Come on, Bunky, you're gonna love her.
Even if you say no to me, too.
I'm not going to do it again.
I'm not gonna do it.
Come on, Banky, it's a fun life
Even if you only tell me about me
Banky, come on, for tomorrow
I'm not doing anything with my life
Come on, Bunky, you first
What's next?
I'm in here somewhere.
I want more.
Hey!
I'm a failure.
You don't know anything about yourself.
You don't know what I think about you.
You can't tell me what to do.
What are you doing?
You'll be fine tomorrow.
Will someone please tell me what's going on?
I'm not going to change.
I'm going to like it.
One-sided
I'm not so self-aware.
Bunky, come on, what if it goes up?
I'm still in love with myself
Let's give it one more shot.
It's important.
Come on, Bunky, what if I do it again?
I hated myself my whole life.
I used to believe that being young was sad.
I used to believe it was important.
I'm such a pain in the ass.
Forgive me.
I'm coming with you.
Come on, let's go
Hey! Hey!
Hey!
It's too bright.
All my life
Sweaty paddles
I'll go with you
I'll still make it by the time we get there
I'll be bunky-dunky
And kiss me
Even if you tell me I can'tEven if they say no.
Start again.
It's better if I can't tell you.
You still want me to tell you.
Even if you tell me not to.
I understand. You've already told them everything.
What's wrong with God?
Hypocrisy with the heart.
It's like he's dead.
Memories can always be mixed up.
Memories can be mixed.
Thank you very much.
About a month after the van announcement.
Good morning, I'm Gusan Kissei, the Cherry Blossom Engineer.
Today, I'm Gusan Kisei, a music video shooter for "Summer as a Shortcut.
Thank you very much.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
It's the first time for me to see the dance moves I've been practicing being made into a video like this.
I am happy that I am there.
I still feel a little strange.
I'm nervous.
Are you happy?
Yes, I am.
I'm still nervous.
I thought it was a great group of people.
It's so hot.
I know it's hard for everyone, but let's make this place the strongest.
Sanken! Matsuhashi Kabuki! Let's go!
Yay!
I have many memories of gymnasiums in different environments.
Like Manakako.
And the photo shoot for the unveiling was also in a gymnasium.
I'm sure it holds a lot of memories for the third term students.
It's easy to get emotionally involved.
Like the last dance.
There were a lot of parts where we went all out as idols.
But I think the fact that we were able to swing like that
I think that our past experiences have given us confidence.
Thank you very much.
Good luck!
Good bye!
That wraps it up for today's shoot.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
I'll do my best to cooperate with you as a third term student.
Thank you very much for today.
Thank you very much.
I think we've definitely grown more than the presentation where we were dancing that van.
I was able to do this with you guys because
And it's because you all taught me.
And Yuzu Shume helped me a lot.
I am full of gratitude.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
Shortly before the release of the music video, the first viewing of my first work
Summer's a chance to breathe
Morning feeling Losing my smile Morning comes early
Cute.
Koko hoho.
Eh! Cute.
Cute.
Amazing.
Light shines on love
That glimmer of clouds
A certain place
A little bit
This road
Wherever it goes
Always a miracle
Chase after it
Let the light shine on love
That glimmer of clouds
Always smiling
Give me
I want to tell you
Every day was a day
172 days of stories end here
But the 11 of us are just beginning to climb the hill.
We're still chasing after you, Rusty.
Rusty, you're turning into the moon... Haruyo yo, don't stop...
We are Sakurazaka 46 third term students